namebirthdaycakes.com 2019-03-12

# Privacy Policy

## 1\. What Information We Collect

We respect the privacy of every individual who uses our Website. We collect certain personal information and non-personal that you voluntarily provide to us.

#### 1.1 Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. 

#### If you generate any image

When user generates any name cakes/wishes we only save the names. We use this to show more related cakes/wishes with that name. We do not disclose your photos, which you have uploaded for generating photo cakes/wishes. We immediately delete photos after generating the final output.

#### If you contact us (via [website form](https://namebirthdaycakes.com/contactus.php))

Name, e-mail address, IP address, information on our communication with you and any additional information you provide us with.

#### If you subscribe to our newsletter

Email address, marketing campaign information such as your interest in our Services.

#### If you subscribe to Push Notifications

Email address, marketing campaign information such as your interest in our Services. If you don't want to receive Push Notifications please [unsubscribe](https://namebirthdaycakes.com/unsub.php).

#### 1.2 Non-personal identification information

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect some information. Such information includes the type of browser you use, your browser’s language, access time or the website from which you linked to us. We also collect information about your computer's operating system and information about your usage and activity on the Site. This information is only used to assist us in providing an effective service. We may, from time to time, supply the owners and operators of third party websites and mobile applications which have a link to our site or application with information about the number of users of our Site or Mobile. You cannot be identified from any of this information. 

## 2\. How We Use Collected Information

NameBirthdayCakes.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes

#### 2.1 To personalize user experience

We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

#### 2.2 To send push notifications

If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive push notifications that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future notifications. We include detailed [unsubscribe](https://namebirthdaycakes.com/unsub.php) instructions.

## 3\. How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information and data stored on our Site. We use a secure server via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

## 4\. Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

## 5\. Cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. These cookies collect information about how people are using our websites, for example which pages are visited most often, how people are moving from one link to another and if a particular user experiences error messages on certain pages. All information these cookies collect is grouped together with information from other people's use of our websites. Overall, these cookies provide us with analytical information about how our websites are performing and how we can improve them.

#### 5.1 How long will cookies stay on your browsing device?

The length of time a cookie will stay on your browsing device depends on whether it is a "persistent" or "session" cookie. Session cookies will only stay on your device until you stop browsing the website that has set the cookie. Persistent cookies stay on your browsing device after you have finished browsing a particular website, until they are deleted or until they expire. 

#### 5.2 Cookies by third parties

Other cookies are placed on your browsing device by third parties when you visit our websites. Third parties setting cookies from our websites will be providing a service to us or a function of the website, but we do not always control how third-party cookies are used. Some third parties may use cookies to help gather information about your browsing activity so that they can deliver website advertising to you that is relevant to your interests.

#### 5.3 How to Manage and Disable Cookies

If you do not want us to recognize your device, please configure your Internet browser to erase all cookies from your device, to block all cookies or to receive a warning before a cookie is stored. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. Refer to the following links for information to deactivate cookies in commonly used browsers:

  * [Mozilla Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored) and [here](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)
  * [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en) and [here](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)

## 6\. Measuring our visitors

We measure visitors to our website using Google Analytics. This records what pages you view within our site, how you arrived at our site and some basic information about your computer. All of that information is anonymous – so we don’t know who you are; just that somebody visited our site.

#### 6.1 Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to recognize you and link the devices you use when you visit our websites or use our Service on your browser or mobile device. Google Analytics facilitates the assignment of data, sessions and interactions across several devices to a pseudonymous user ID and thus the analysis of activities across devices. We share a unique identifier, like a user ID or hashed email address, with Google to facilitate the service. The generated information is usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there. As IP anonymization is activated on this website, Google will reduce your IP address within the Member States of the European Union or in other states party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area beforehand. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. The IP address transmitted by your browser in the context of Google Analytics is not merged with other Google data. Google will use the collected data on our behalf to evaluate the use of the websites, to compile reports on website activity and to provide the website operator with other services related to website and Internet use. 

You can learn more about [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html "Google Analytics' privacy policy") or [opt out if you wish](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "How to opt out of Google Analytics").

## 7\. Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers

#### 7.1 Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

## 8\. Compliance with GDPR

Under the GDPR, you have various rights in relation to your Personal Information, such as the rights of access, rectification, restriction, objection, portability, and erasure. Please note that these rights are subject to certain limitations set forth in applicable law.

To exercise these rights, please [contact us](mailto:contact@namebirthdaycakes.com). We will seek to deal with your request without undue delay, and in any event in accordance with the requirements of applicable laws. Please note that we may keep a record of your communications to help us resolve any issues you raise.

## 9\. Compliance with children's online privacy protection act

We do not intend to solicit or collect Personal Information from anyone under the age of 16. If you are under 16, do not enter information on this Website or engage our services. If you believe a child or yours under the age of 18 has entered Personal Information, please contact us to have the data removed and terminate the child's account.

## 10\. Changes to this privacy policy

NameBirthdayCakes.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## 11\. Your acceptance of these policies

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: [contact@namebirthdaycakes.com](mailto:contact@namebirthdaycakes.com)

This document was last updated on May 25, 2018
